

NGUYĒN HƯƠNG Software Developer / Writer / Editor

9/4/1999

8

0961578499

dieuhuong2h@outlook.com

🚹 101A Phuong Mai, Ha Noi

https://aislingvt.vercel.app/res ume?cv=huong

# Skills

HTML, CSS, SCSS



English



JavaScript, TypeScript, ReactJs, Git, Figma, NextJS



Java, Python, JSP, Postman, Firebase, JSON, BIRT report, Angular, SQL



Vue, C#, MongoDBXML, JQuery, NodeJs



My Language skill: C1
English (proficient), N5
Japanese

### **OBJECTIVE**

I have been designing and creating websites for over 1 years. I have experience designing and writing websites mainly in ReactJS, and have skills regarding video editing, writing and photoshop!

I'm looking to join an inclusive company which doesn't discriminate peoples based on their race / gender / culture as a freelancer / salaryperson!

My English proficiency includes good communication skills in both listening and speaking, and the ability to read and write documents in English.

Additionally, I am proficient in using project management tools such as Git, IDEs such as Visual Studio Code, and various designer tools such as Photoshop, Figma, and can do a bit of sound / video editing!

## **EDUCATION**

09/2017 - 4/2023

**FPT UNIVERSITY - HOA LAC** | Software Engineering Major Bachelor's degree certificates. GPA: 6,94

#### **WORK EXPERIENCES**

04/2023 - 09/2024

WORKING AT FPT FIS (1+ YEAR) | Fresher / Employee

- I gained valuable experience collaborating and contributing effectively as part of a team, working on both front-end and back-end tasks.
- I honed my skill in React.js development and experienced in utilizing various other front-end tools, backed by practical work experience in a professional setting.

04/2022 - 07/2022

#### 3 MONTHS OF FRESHER AT CMC GLOBAL | Fresher

- During this job, I became familiar with corporate procedures and completed online courses to enhance my skills.
- Additionally, I gained valuable insight into teamwork and developed the ability to effectively contribute as a member of a team. I also involved with a project to enhance my ReactJS / NextJS skill.

01/2020 - 07/2022

### 3 MONTHS OF INTERNSHIP AT FSOFT | Intern

- I had the opportunity to immerse myself in various office tasks and environments, allowing me to gain valuable work experience, learn about work ethics and responsibilities.
- I also had the chance to work with tools like Git and utilize popular Integrated Development Environments (IDEs) such as NetBeans, VSCode, and PyCharm, which provided me with valuable hands-on experience.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

I'm Able to work with Different object-oriented programming languages such as Python, Java/Typescript, ReactJS,...

I know how to integrate RESTful API and utilizes communication

techniques between FE and BE and know now to use tools like Postman,...

I'm Familiar with project management models such as SCRUM, AGILE, Waterfall,...

I'm capable of Using Project management tools like Github, Gitlab or Git, and willing to learn different tools.

I'm also a quick learner, and capable of using different AI tools like Chatgpt, characterAI and more

I have skills in video editing using Wondershare Filmora, and have some photoshop skills, and Audio editing skills using Audacity.

Video Editing Examples: https://shorturl.at/JoVoW

## **SOFT SKILLS & QUALITIES**

My Language skill: C1 English (proficient), N5 Japanese

I have Proficient English skills, knowledgeable in using writing tools, such as Grammar.ly,...

Examples of my writings: https://shorturl.at/zRGBQ

Although A bit introverted, when it comes to work ethics, I'm meticulous and observant about any assigned task, and persistent in getting works done.

I'm Able to work both independently or in a team environment.

## **PROJECTS**

.....

THESE ARE MY PERSONAL PROJECTS, PROJECTS THAT I HAVE PARTAKEN IN DURING MY WORKEXPERIENCE AND OTHER PROJECTS DURING MY UNIVERSITY EDUCATION:

- Developed a user management web front using ReactJS for Dat Xanh Group: http://uat-admin.datxanh.com.vn/
- Blogging website (registered domain): https://duyhung2h.web.app/, written in ReactJs.
- Blogging website (registered domain): https://aislingvt.vercel.app/, written in ReactJs + NextJS + Vercel.
- Comic reading website: A Frontend project for reading different comics
- House rental website: A simple Frontend project for landlords to manage financial details.
- Nhà Hàng Ba Miền website: A Fullstack website platform for customers and managers, specialising in online food delivery
- Black League Shop website: A Fullstack website shoe shop platform for customers
- Project André: A Python project for my upcoming modded game project



All of my different day-to-day hobbies!

- Playing and modifying video games
- Reading, writing in English
- History, world's cultures and geography
- Listening to podcasts and music
- Painting and arts

© topcv.vn